SUCCESS Should open amezon url and verifying the title of page
SUCCESS Should hover mouse on "Sign In button" button
SUCCESS Verifying if "Sign In button" button present
SUCCESS Should hover mouse on "ToolTip textbox" button
SUCCESS Verifying if "ToolTip textbox" button present
SUCCESS Should click on "Today's Deals" tab from amezon main page
SUCCESS Verifying if "Today's Deal" page opened
SUCCESS Should click on "Book" checkbox from department to checkoff
SUCCESS Shoul select "Klutz LEGO Chain Reactions Craft Kit" from the list
SUCCESS Should enter "Nike Shoes" in to search box
SUCCESS Should click on "Search button"
SUCCESS Verifying if some items displayed in results